It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those
good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who
positively can do
All the things that make us
Laugh and cry
He's a family guy
And now
back to Romancing the Stone.
The only way they're not going to kill
my sister is if we give them the stone.
Well, they're going to be
looking everywhere.
We'll have to hide it in my chin.
Uh-oh, here they come.
You'd better get in there, too.
Good God, Joan Wilder's sister is
being held hostage in Cartagena,
and there's not a policeman in sight.
I guess it's up to me.
- Good evening, I'm Tom Tucker.
- And I'm Diane Simmons.
Our top story, Mayor West has dispatched
the entire Quahog Police Force
to Cartagena, Colombia,
to assist in the rescue
of fictional 1984 movie character,
Elaine Wilder.
More on that later.
Now let's go to Ollie Williams'
Cooking Corner.
- What are you making, Ollie?
- Eggo!
Thanks, Ollie. And now this.
Lois, can you come out here
for a second?
Hey, Lois, can you run inside
and get me some oranges
or whatever it is these things eat?
Peter, what is that?
This would be a giraffe, Isaac Newton.
I stole it from the zoo.
What with Mayor West
sending all the cops away,
everybody can do whatever they want.
Peter, I don't care
what Mayor West has done.
You can't just break the law.
Sure, I can. I've been doing it all week.
Like yesterday, I started a lovable gang
of cockney pickpockets.
All right, boys,
the best targets are old, rich people.
There's one now. Go get him.
Oh, no, there's no police here to help me!
I hope you don't find the money
strapped to my thigh.
Peter, you take that thing back
where it belongs immediately.
All right, I guess we gotta go
back to the zoo, Allison Janney.
Allison Janney?
Good morning, honey.
That feels really good. What...
Hey! Hey! Hey! What the hell?
You're not the same giraffe
from last night. Get out of here!
What the hell?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
I gotta stop taking my baths
during Peter's shenanigans.
Hello. Oh, hey, Jillian. What's up?
Brian, are you coming over
to watch Laguna Beach tonight?
What time does it start?
10:00 Eastern and specific time.
What? What did you say? Specific time?
Don't you mean Pacific time?
No, I think it's called specific time.
They mean it starts specifically at 10:00.
- Stewie, are you on the line?
- Yes.
Jillian, I'll talk to you later.
So, Meg...
- How was school?
- Horrible.
There's a dance Friday night
and no one wants to go with me.
Even my backup guy had plans.
Hi, Jimmy.
I heard you didn't have a date
to the dance,
and I was wondering
if you'd like to go with me.
Oh, I...
Hang on.
I'd love to go, Meg, but I have to go
to my little brother's funeral that night.
I'm sure you'll find someone
to go with you.
No, I won't. I'm so fat and gross.
I should just kill myself.
- That's... Come on.
- I'm gonna do it.
I'm gonna kill myself
'cause no one will go with me.
Meg, stop it. Come on.
All right, all right, Meg, look, what if I...
What if I drove you
and walked in with you or whatever?
Brian, will you go with me?
- Are you going to kill yourself if I don't?
- Yeah.
Well, then my hands are pretty much tied.
Brian, thank you, thank you, thank you.
I have to buy a new dress.
All the ones I have make me look fat.
The story on everyone's mind
continues to be
the absence of police officers in Quahog.
Sir, as a citizen,
how has this affected you?
The police are gone?
Oh, my God, we're finally safe!
Hey, Joe, where you been?
We haven't seen you in days.
Ever since Mayor West
deployed the police to Cartagena,
I've been working nonstop.
The only reason I didn't have to go myself
is that South America
isn't wheelchair accessible.
Hey, you guys, we should help Joe out.
We could be cops, right, Joe?
Well, we have started
an emergency training program
at the police academy,
but I'm not sure
that you're cut out for the job.
Come on, we'll be great cops.
Besides, it's bound to go better
than my deep-sea training.
Well, we've got a long time
in this decompression chamber.
You guys mind if I turn on the radio?
Peter, don't!
- Nice going, jackass.
- Look what you did.
Hey. Hey, excuse the hell out of me
for trying to brighten your day
with music, all right?
- You idiot, use your brain.
- You're an idiot.
- Stop, stop, stop.
- Stop, stop, stop, stop.
Man, we're going to need some
butter or something.
Brian, it is so nice of you
to take Meg to this dance.
It really means a lot to her.
- You got any weed?
- I put it in your coat pocket.
Here she is.
Brian, I present to you your polished
turd for the evening.
- How do I look, Brian?
- You sure do, Meg.
FYI, the carpet matches the drapes
in color and quantity.
Ever seen a blacksmith's apron?
Well, Brian, here we go.
This is going to be so much fun.
God, this is going to be a long night.
Brian, let's dance. This song kicks ass.
Man, I gotta tell you,
I can see why you'd be insecure, Meg.
Some of these chicks are unbelievable.
Brian, can I ask you something?
Are you drinking so much
because you don't want to be here?
No, no, Meg. It's... That's...
My God, look at these chicks.
You know the best thing
about these girls is,
even if you're terrible,
they don't know the difference.
You know, Meg,
there's no dogs allowed here,
so you're going to have to leave.
But Brian can stay.
You know, Connie, I think I have a theory
about why you're such a bitch.
- Excuse me?
- Brian, let's just go.
No, no, no, no, no. Now, hang on.
Hang on, Meg, hang on.
You see, Connie, you're popular
because you developed early
and started giving hand jobs
when you were 12.
But now you can't stand
to look at yourself in the mirror
because all you see is a whore.
So, you pick on Meg
to avoid the inevitable realization
that once your body's used up by age 19,
you're gonna be a worn-out,
chalky-skinned burlap sack
that even your stepdad won't want.
How's that? Am I in the ballpark?
Brian, that was amazing.
No one's ever stood up for me like that.
Hey, no problem. She's a... She's a skank.
You know, you don't... You don't deserve...
You don't deserve all the crap you get,
Meg, you know that?
Thanks, Brian.
Sorry, that was the booze, not you.
You gonna eat that?
Yes, the day can begin.
Good morning, Brian.
Now, we can do this one of two ways.
I can bust your balls to pieces right now
or we can spread it out
over the course of the day.
- I don't wanna talk about it.
- Well, I do.
So, tell me everything
that happened at the dance.
- Morning, cutie.
- Yeah, hey.
I had so much fun last night, Brian.
Hey, I thought maybe we can go
get some coffee later.
I don't think so.
Come on. Who's a good boy?
Who's a good boy? Huh?
- Who's a good boy?
- Me.
- Yes, yes, who's a good boy?
- I am, I'm a good boy.
But, no, no. Look, I got stuff to do today.
All right? Sorry.
Well, we should hook up anyway.
I'll bug you later.
Well, she seems to have
taken a shine to you, Brian.
With a little encouragement,
you might get her
to put her cankles behind her ears.
Stewie, shut up.
Who the hell is texting me at 8:00 a. M?
Wait a minute,
something did happen last night.
Look, it's not that big a deal, all right?
We just...
We just made out a little.
- Tell me about it. Go!
- It didn't mean anything.
I had a few too many and...
It's not even worth going into.
This is an even bigger jackpot
than when the Emperor figured out
the formula for great Star Wars dialogue.
Something, something, something,
dark side.
complete.
Well, this is it.
Our first day of Police Academy 4.
Welcome to the police academy.
We're gonna start
by learning how to do a cavity search.
Peter, you will be the police officer
and Quagmire, you will be the suspect.
Begin.
Sir, I suspect you are
in possession of drugs
and I'm gonna have to
give you a full cavity search.
Drop your pants.
Peter, you don't have to
pull your pants down.
- Sorry. I'm still learning.
All right, start the search.
I think that's everything.
You want me
to double check?
I appreciate you guys volunteering
for this next phase of training,
which will address
how to deal with a crazed drug user.
Hey, Joe,
what are we supposed to do in here?
You see that coffee you're drinking?
I have, without your knowledge,
added a large amount of PCP
to one of those cups of coffee.
I won't say which one,
but in a few moments,
one of you will completely lose
your freaking mind. Good luck.
This is not good.
- We're in trouble.
- All right, let's all try and relax here, right?
I don't feel so good.
- God, it's Cleveland, it's him, it's him!
- Shut up, maybe it's you.
How the hell did all this skin
get on my arm?
Quagmire, put your skin back on.
One of us is about to freak out.
- Hi, honey.
- What?
I was thinking about our kiss last night.
I never knew how flat
and wide your tongue was.
Yeah.
You know, I've thought about
how you stood up for me at the dance
and all the nice things you said.
We should totally be
boyfriend and girlfriend.
Well, Meg...
You know what's strange?
I think I might be gay.
I saw this penis on the internet today
and I thought to myself,
"Well, that's... That's just fine. "
I'm going to the mall later.
Maybe you can come
and help me pick out some underwear.
I don't think that's gonna be a possibility.
I have plans...
With Chris.
Chris and I have plans this afternoon.
- We do?
- Yeah, we're doing that thing.
We're doing what you usually do
on a Thursday afternoon.
- Masturbate?
- Masturbate.
We're gonna masturbate together.
Well, maybe back to back,
but I gotta tell you, I'm not 100% on this.
There's the cute prom couple.
Hi, Mom. Is it cool if Brian and I
go to the mall this afternoon?
- Actually, I thought I was pretty clear...
- Of course, it's okay.
Ever since that dance,
you two have become such good friends.
Who would have thought?
We're more than friends, Mom.
Last night, at the dance, Brian...
Last night, we decided to be best friends.
Right, Meg?
Come on, let's go to the mall.
We'll get you a...
- Get you a big old pretzel.
- I want a pretzel, too.
Brian, I'm ready. You in or out?
- Everyone, this is Brian.
- This is Brian.
- He does look like Ben Affleck.
- He looks just like Ben Affleck.
- Is that Ben Affleck?
- Hey.
- So, how did you guys meet?
- I'm a friend of her dad's.
He's older.
- He's cute.
- Do you have a brother?
Make-up and stickers and ponies
and myspace. Com.
Brian's the first serious boyfriend
I've ever had.
Meg, can I talk to you for a second?
Look, this has gone a little too far.
I like you, I think you're great.
But what happened at the dance was...
I mean, that kiss was just a mistake.
Oh, no, did I do something wrong?
Was it because
I didn't sniff your butt first?
What? No. I mean, yes. That's how I would
know you were interested.
But, Meg, the fact is you and I are friends
and that's the way it needs to stay.
Besides, I have a girlfriend,
I'm dating Jillian.
All right, Brian. I understand.
Good. I'm gonna grab Stewie
and then we can go.
What's that Brian? You were just kidding?
I knew you were.
I love you, too, Brian, and you love me.
You do love me, Brian.
- Hey, Brian.
- Oh, Meg. Hey.
Hey, listen, I hope you're feeling all right
about our little talk the other day.
You know,
about us being just friends and all.
Yeah. No, I'm fine, I'm fine.
And, hey, look I... I wanted to thank you
for being so great to me.
- So, I baked you a pie.
- Wow. Hey, that looks delicious.
Wow, this is good. What's in there?
Well, there some apples
and some cinnamon and my hair.
- What?
- My hair's in the pie, Brian.
And now it's inside of you.
Part of me is inside of you, Brian.
Do you feel me, Brian?
Do you feel me inside of you?
You got some pie, huh?
Can I have a piece?
- Sure.
- Let me have some of that Cool Whip.
- What'd you say?
- You can't have a pie without Cool Whip.
- Cool Whip?
- Cool Whip, yeah.
- You mean, Cool Whip.
- Yeah, Cool Whip.
- Cool Whip.
You're saying it weird. Why are you
putting so much emphasis on the "H"?
What are you talking about?
I'm just saying it, Cool Whip.
You put Cool Whip on pie.
Pie tastes better with Cool Whip.
- Say "whip".
- Whip.
- Now say "Cool Whip".
- Cool Whip.
You're eating hair!
Well, Lois, I am now a graduate
of the Quahog Police Academy
and an official on-duty cop.
I can't believe I'm married
to a big, scary police officer.
Just keep your eyes on the eggs, ma'am.
Yes, Officer.
- You are such a dirty cop.
- Don't break those yolks, ma'am.
Oh, my God, Lois, I hit you.
I know.
Now stick your finger in there and twist it.
Hey, Lois. Can I talk to you for a second?
I think we may have a problem with Meg.
You're telling me?
She's been locked in her room all day.
Who knows what she's doing up there?
Yeah, well, the thing is, Meg is becoming
a little enamored with me
and I'm kind of
losing control of the situation.
She's just grateful
you took her to the dance.
Well, I think it's more than that.
So here's the thing, and don't get mad,
and that part I can't stress enough...
That's a great shirt, by the way.
I may have made out with Meg.
Okay, I had that coming.
What the hell is wrong with you?
You sick bastard.
- Look, I was drinking...
- What a shock.
Look, the short version is this morning
she made me eat her hair pie...
No, it's not what you think.
Stewie had some, too.
Stop punching me.
Look, Brian, I don't know
what the hell happened between you two
but you better go upstairs
and straighten it out right now.
This is even worse than when you ate
that bubble-gum out of the garbage.
Brian, did you get
into the garbage last night?
- No. Why?
- Don't lie to me, Brian.
I'm not lying.
Meg, you got a minute?
What the hell?
- I made that for you, Brian.
- Meg!
Look, you obviously didn't
hear me yesterday. So I'll explain it again.
And here to assist me is
Headmaster of the New York School for
the Hard of Hearing, Mr. Garrett Morris.
- Meg, we're not boyfriend and girlfriend.
- We're not boyfriend and girlfriend!
- I will never be attracted to you.
- I will never be attracted to you!
- You're acting like a psycho bitch.
- You're acting like a psycho bitch!
Goodnight and have a pleasant tomorrow.
Goodnight and have a pleasant tomorrow!
- I won't be ignored, Brian.
- I like your ass.
Joe, I gotta tell you.
This whole cop thing ain't as exciting
as I thought it was gonna be.
When do we get to shoot some bad guys?
Guys, it's not all about action.
It's about staying vigilant
until you're needed.
- What are you doing?
- I'm watching Bonnie undress.
- Bonnie's your wife.
- I know.
I like to watch her strip and pretend
she's a woman who I've never met
but who looks just like Bonnie
and lives in my house.
Get naked, you strange whore!
Peter, I haven't seen Meg or Brian
since last night.
I think something may have happened.
Mom, is it bad if I saw Meg
tie up Brian last night,
put him in the trunk of his car
and then drive away?
What? Chris, why didn't you say anything?
I dropped the ball, I'm sorry.
I have just been buried in paperwork
for the past 72 hours.
Oh, my God. Brian was right.
Meg really must be obsessed with him.
Peter, we gotta find them.
Don't worry, Lois, we're the police
and we'll do our very best
to find Brian and girl-Chris.
I'm really having
a great time tonight, Brian.
I can't believe you went to all this trouble.
- Well, you know me.
- I do, Brian. I know you so well.
- So, are you ready?
- For what?
For the fun we're gonna have, Brian.
We're gonna have fun tonight.
Good old-fashioned, all-American fun.
Listen, Meg, I'm not gonna lie to you, here.
I'm a little uncomfortable.
Just relax.
We're gonna be here for a while.
- Well, I don't know if... Wait, what?
- We're gonna be here for a while.
- A while?
- Yeah, a while.
- You mean a while?
- A while.
- Brian, you're acting weird.
Come on,
that one doesn't even have an "H" in it.
- Don't move, dirtbag.
- Holy crap, what the hell is this?
Brian, she's a teenager.
Yeah, Brian, you're doing the same thing
that Mia Farrow did to that Chinaman
that Woody Allen brought home
from the circus.
Peter, hold on to that thought,
because I'm going to explain to you
when we get home all the things
that are wrong with that statement.
But, first, Meg, you need to let Brian go.
- But Mom, I love him!
- Honey, you're just confused.
I'm not confused.
I've never been more certain
about anything in my life.
I need him.
Meg, I know that's what you think
right now, but you're...
God, I wish I could make you understand.
You don't know what you need.
- I know what she needs.
- You do?
You bet. Bring her by my house
around 8:30 tonight, I'll take care of her.
Hi, Mr. Quagmire.
Mom said I should come over here?
Have a seat, Meg.
Soon, it'll all become clear.
Excuse me,
while I get a little more comfortable.
Meg, I've watched you grow up
from a playful little girl
into a very special young woman.
Now, you probably just think of me as
"square old Mr. Quagmire from next door,"
but, I've been around the block
a few times, learned a couple things.
And I can tell you this,
there's no reason to grow up too fast.
Teenage girls are exposed
to so much these days
I can see why a relationship
looks glamorous.
But, you've got all the time in the world,
and a lot of wonderful experiences
ahead of you.
Hang on, I wanna give you something.
This book helped me
when I was about your age.
It let me know
that as long as I kept on rolling,
I'd find that one person
who would make me whole.
- Thanks, Mr. Quagmire.
- You don't have to thank me.
Now, get on out of here, you little scamp.
All right, ladies, you ready for action?
We sure are, Glenn. Do you have the whip?
Got it right... Wait, what?
Hello, I'm Tom Tucker. Coming up at 11:00,
Quahog police return to active duty
after giving up the search
for fictitious Romancing the Stone
character, Elaine Wilder.
Plus, in national news,
America's Scoutmasters are asking,
"Why are the kids so shy in the shower?"
And, in entertainment,
is Annette Bening made of leather?
A local tanner has a surprising revelation.
We'll have all this, and what else, Ollie?
Sports!
- And sports. Join us at 11:00.
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru